Hello, this is Tsutsuki Ayume.
Coffee shop
As this is the third installment, I'm here today to eat my favorite shaved ice. Yay!
Today, I didn't come alone, I brought that girl who is a good friend of mine, so here we go!
Ta-da! I'm Airei Seimi. I'm so happy to be here.
First running girl. This is Demekin-san here. This shaved ice shop is very popular.
Of course, I've seen it on social media, and you went there the other day, right? Yes, I came here about 6 days ago, and I'm so glad I did.
Then, what do you recommend? Do you want to explore a new menu? Yes, I want to try different flavors.
Yes, I do. Shall we go right away?
Excuse me for interrupting.
Good morning.
Thank you.
What'll it be?
I already know what I want.
But you know what? I'd like to share.
Yes, one piece at a time, please.
Okay.
Half.
I'll have
I'll have a slice.
One hour.
But not that one?
Half.
One axis and
What's normal?
Normal?
- No changes.
- Okay. - Okay. Thank you very much. - Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to it too much. I'm too excited.
- You went to all the trouble of making a reservation? Alone. - I made a reservation.
- You ate this all by yourself? - I made a reservation. You ate this all by yourself? Yes, right around here.
- Same girl. - Same girl. Same girl.
- You should've noticed. - I'm embarrassed.
- But you're so sweet. But you're so sweet. You leave me alone.
- I'm nervous. - I'm embarrassed.
- I haven't eaten breakfast yet. - I'll have breakfast and lunch too.
- I opened the shaved ice sauce. - I see.
- I had shaved ice the day before yesterday too. - You eat too much.
I can't do it all by myself.
- I'd like to have two kinds. I can't do it alone. - Really?
Really? Oh no.
- I'll have some. Kakizunda sauce. - Thank you.
- Very good. It's amazing.
- What's on it? - It's half of this.
This is a half. It's a half of a half.
This visual. Isn't it amazing?
It's the best.
- Let's try again.
Once again, it's private, isn't it?
It's private. I'm sorry.
I have a folder in my album called "Shaved Ice.
Let me see.
Sure, go ahead.
Wow, it's growing. I'll take a photo of it.
Is that okay?
Yeah, it's okay.
Wait a minute. What? What? I think I'm here for a magazine shoot.
I'm off the record. Kid's goal.I'm off the hook. Gaki goal.
Kid goal. It's true.
Could it be what I see in front of me?
I had it last time.
Fig pie.
What did you have last time?
Figs and pumpkin.
Pumpkin.
Pumpkin. Pumpkin. It's a pumpkin now.
Why pumpkin?
It's a pumpkin.
Oh, really?
Thank you very much.
It's amazing. It's sparkling.
The distance from one axis to the other. It's the season.
Would you like some?
Yes, I do. Bon appétit.
Where do I start? Where do I start?
It's falling apart.
Oh no!
Wait a minute.
Ready.
What food will you eat next time?
Oh! A shaft!
Oh, no!
Axis! Not uniaxial flavor.
It's uniaxial!
It's already a zunda, too!
I can't always react.
Because I'm alone, I can't react. I'm alone. I'm just trying to get a good reaction.
It's a little embarrassing.
I know!
I'm so happy! To be able to react like this.
To be able to react like this.
I'm falling apart.
Mmm. How's it look?
Oh, it's so red.
This is loaded with tofu cream.
Does it tip?
Oh, sorry.
There you go.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah, it's delicious.
Wow.
A shaft.
I'm really impressed.
Za.
Za?
Fruit.
It's the best. I love it.
There's something on top of the paste. What is it?
That's right.
There are so many layers!
There's a lot of it inside.
Oh, really?
Yum! A little salty.
Yeah, it's great!
Miso.
Are you telling the truth?Are you telling the truth?
It's a little salty.
Really?
There's a Japanese uniaxial
It's full of them.
Yes.
I want to show you.
There's a lot of them.
Wow, I can't see.
You're right.
Hold it.
Delicious!
It's good.
I found something amazing.
What is it?
It's got jell-o in it.
Yes, it is.
What's that?
It's in there.
Pull, pull, pull, pull!
What is that?
It looks like tea.
Delicious.
Excuse me, what's in this?
What is it?
It's a temporary vacancy.
A pause?
Tea jelly.
Tea jelly. I knew it. I knew it.Tea jelly, I knew it, yes, it was right.
Lovely!
This cream on top is the body of miso sesame!
That's great!
It's great, it fits.
Isn't it amazing?
It's amazing to think about.
It's a great combination!
I'm excited just looking at the menu.
I don't know.
It's a spinning wheel.
Spin around!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's right.
You can't go from one-hawk to the other.
One-hawk.
YouTube.
You know, the first thing you two did together.
You know what we did?
At the convenience store.
I miss that.
That was great.
What?
They were like...
I don't know why.
Complaining.
I mean, really.
We're such good friends.
Not like two years ago.
It was a long time ago.very forward
Young.
I'd like to do it again. convenience store
2023 version
Really? Your taste buds have changed?
Not really.
That's why I don't know what I like now.
When you go to a convenience store
What kind of onigiri would you choose?
Hmmm...
O-guan-bu
Ah...
Second place, second place
Yaki Onigiri
Don't say it!
You missed it.
I had it yesterday.
He was so excited to eat it.
Oh, what?
I found something.
It's salty.
Here.
Did you do it?
Yeah, I did.
That's it.
What is this?
Does it have a soy-sauce flavor?
Like Mitakashi-ish?
Oh, look.Oh, look.
It tastes like tofu.
Yes, it does.
That's good.
What was the correct answer?
Dashi-dofu.
I can feel the broth.
It's amazing.
It's a meal. Just one of these.
That's right.
I always come here for lunch.
Oh, I see.
But, you know, this place, you guys...
Be careful. It's a point of interest.
You know, two half-size or...
Or one regular size.
Or regular one.
Ayame, come alone.
This, this...
I had to eat two by myself.
It was a little bit difficult for her.
Filled with shaved ice.
Wow!
What's that again... hmm? Scene...
Azuki?
Show him your face.
Not at all.Not at all.
I've been looking at you the whole time.
Bon appétit.
Where is it?
Scoop.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You don't mind, do you? Don't touch me like this.
There it is.
You found it, didn't you?
I already know all at once.
You feel that?
Yeah, I can feel it.
You feel it?
Yeah, it's adzuki beans.
It's so smooth.
That's... That's different.
That's good, too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay, thank you.
Which one is it?
Are there any others?
There aren't many. They're rare.
Oh, I just left you.
Oh, all at once.
No, I don't think so.
But eat it. Two adzuki beans, please.
What's this?
It's crazy.
Wait a minute.Hold on a sec.
Yeah, I'm out.
Not yet.
Laughing.
Not yet, really.
Oh, my God.
This is the store.
You said earlier you wanted a T-shirt from this store.
Yeah, I did.
You said I should've bought it.
I thought the T-shirt and the chocolate bag were really cute.
I thought the chocolate bag was really cute.
I wasn't sure if I should buy it.
You could've moved.
I could have worn it today.
You're right.
It's supposed to be 35 degrees today.
Really?
It's September.
It's September, it's October.
Oh, man.
I can't wait.
It's Christmas.
I'm looking forward to it.
But first...
I've got to feel the Autumn vibes.
Autumn already.
I gotta feel it.
Autumn... it's only here for a moment, isn't it?Autumn is like that for a moment, isn't it?
So much more than usual.
I don't know if you'll ever come back, doggie.
I love fall.
What is it?
Maple leaves.
What? I want to go to one of those.
Wow, wow, wow.
You know what I said a long time ago about candle warmers?
I told you about the candle warmer, right?
I got those in the mail.
I'll go get it.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Whoever's watching this has no idea what we're talking about.
Candles?
Candles, heated by heat.
Don't light it.
And melt them.
This way, it's not dangerous.
And the smell spreads... it smells so good.
I'm using candles.
Why did you...
You wanted to give it to me.
I didn't have any candles.
I didn't have a candle.
Yes, I do.
I thought it would go with your room.
You do?
There's two of them and a box.
I told my mom... when she came to clean up the other day.My mom came to clean the other day.
She asked me why I have two of these.
I got them in the summer.
I don't do candles in the summer.
I thought
I was like...
It's hot, it's winter.
That's why.
I'll bring them when it's cooler.
I'm so glad.
Matching.
There?
I'm so glad.
Are you okay then?
Yeah, I'm fine.
It's a beautiful day, really.
It's a nice day for youtube again.
Yoneda, I want to go somewhere for breakfast.
Okay, next... a chain coffee shop.
I want to wake up with Yoneda's tattoo.
I want to wake up with Yoneda's tattoos... and eggs on pizza toast... for two.
I've been saying that for a while... but it's never been the right time.
Here we are!
Thank you for the food.
I'll be back. Are there many tote bags?
Bags are 3,600 yen. Sina is 3,500 yen.
T-shirts are 3,500 yen.
Can I buy a T-shirt for 3,500 yen? Can I buy one?
Can I buy one?
One at a time. First place, first prize. One at a time. First place, first place, first place!
Yes, it was delicious!
I also bought these sorry goods!
I will definitely come back again for private visits!
I'm looking forward to the shaved ice in the fall!
It's a little bit late, because we've already filled up with the next fruit...
I'm looking forward to it.
I hope we can come again, just the two of us.
You'll come again?
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
So today is coffee shop No. 3.
Rei-chan and I came for shaved ice.
Thank you very much.
Subscribe to our channel and rate us highly!
Please do.
Bye bye!